thisis50.ning.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - ThisIs50.com

**THISIS50.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

Last updated: November 1, 2013

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to all information learned about or obtained from you when you visit the ThisIs50.com website (the “Site”), whether you access the Site through a personal computer, mobile device or any other means. The Site is provided by Tomorrow, Today Entertainment, Inc. (“Tomorrow, Today”). If you visit the Site, you accept this Policy and the ThisIs50.com Website [Terms of Use](http://www.thisis50.com/main/authorization/termsOfService?noBack=1) (the “Terms of Use”), so please read this Policy and the Terms of Use carefully. Tomorrow, Today may modify the Policy from time to time, effective upon posting to the Site. Your access to or use of the Site at any time constitutes acceptance of the Policy in effect at that time. If you do not wish to be bound by this Policy, do not access or use the Site. This Policy does not apply to information collected offline or through any means other than through the Site.

**Children**

The Site is not directed at children and is offered only to users 13 years of age or older. By providing personal information through the Site, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13. You can find out more about online privacy for children from the Federal Trade Commission at [www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy](http://www.ftc.gov/kidzprivacy).

**Collection of Personal Information**

Information You Provide: Tomorrow, Today receives and stores any information you post on or provide through the Site, including, without limitation, your personal information. For example, you may choose to register as a member of the Site, and you may need to register in order to access or use certain portions of the Site. When you register, we may request information such as your name, email address, mailing address, demographic information, your relationship status, favorite 50 Cent song and other information for your profile. You may also provide personal information if you contact us with a question or to provide input on the Site. In addition, the Site includes interactive and community features, which may include the ability to comment on posts on the Site, interact with other members of the Site on the Site forum and comment on other member profiles. The Site may also allow you to invite your friends to register or participate on the Site. We will use the contact information you provide for your friends to send such invitations.

You understand that information you include in your profile or post or send through interactive and community portions of the Site may be available to the public and that any personal information you disclose, such as your name or email address, may be collected and used by others, including, without limitation, for unsolicited communication with you. By disclosing such personal information, you consent to the publication and distribution of your personal information as described above. You are solely responsible for all information you provide and for any content you post to the Site.

We may also conduct contests, sweepstakes and surveys through the Site. When you choose to participate in a contest, sweepstake or survey, we may request contact information, such as your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number, and demographic and other types of information. Any personal information collected for this purpose may be associated with information you have provided when you registered with the Site.

You may also provide personal information if you make a purchase through the Site. Areas of our Site where visitors can make purchases are run by third parties. Personal information collected on other areas of the Site is not shared with such third parties. Any information you provide on or through any such purchase area of the Site is subject to the privacy policy, available though a link on that portion of the Site, that applies to information collected and used in such area.

Tomorrow, Today may, but is not obligated to, retain the content of any emails you send or information you post or submit to the Site.

Automated Collection. Tomorrow, Today automatically receives and stores certain types of information whenever you visit the Site, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the IP address of the computer you are using and the browser and operating system you are using; the date and time you access the Site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked to the Site. We may associate this information with your personal information. Tomorrow, Today uses “cookies” to automatically gather some of this information. A cookie is a small text file that the Site sends to your computer to collect information about your activities on the Site. The cookie transmits this information back to the Site each time your browser requests a page from the Site, and the information is stored to help facilitate your use of the Site the next time you visit.

The Site may display advertising provided by third party advertising companies. These companies use information about your use of the Site and other websites (but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) to serve targeted advertisements of interest to you. You can learn more about such third party advertising or how you can “opt out” from allowing advertisers to collect this information about you or use it to display advertisements to you at the NAI website at this link: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>.

You can set your browser to not accept cookies, but then you may not be able to access or use certain portions of the Site. You can also delete currently stored cookies. If you disable or delete cookies, you will have disabled the cookies used by NAI to help prevent unwanted advertising. To avoid this, be sure you do not disable or delete the NAI cookie, or add NAI to the approved list of sites form which you will accept cookies.

Corrections/Updates. You may request that Tomorrow, Today delete or modify your personal information, such as your name or email address in accordance with our [Correction/Update Procedure](http://www.thisis50.com/main/authorization/privacyPolicy?noBack=1#correctionupdate).

**Use of Personal Information**

Tomorrow, Today may share your personal information with companies that perform marketing services, fulfillment and payment processing services and other business operations for Tomorrow, Today and with entities such as G-Unit Records, Inc., G-Unit Brands, Inc. and other entities under common ownership or control with Tomorrow, Today (collectively, “Site Affiliates”). Tomorrow, Today and such Site Affiliates may use your personal information to:

• Administer, maintain and improve the Site and its operation;  
• Send you newsletters and other information we think may be of interest to you;  
• Notify you of promotions, new releases, updates or special offers of Tomorrow, Today or Site Affiliates or of our advertisers;  
• Conduct any sweepstake, contest or survey you have entered, for example to contact you if you win;  
• Verify your identity, respond to your requests and otherwise communicate with you;  
• Comply with applicable laws, statutes and regulations;  
• Process orders and payments for purchases through the Site;  
• Enforce the Terms of Use, Tomorrow, Today’s rights and the rights of others;  
• For other purposes disclosed at the time you provide your personal information; and  
• As specifically provided in the Terms of Use and as you may otherwise agree.

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**

Tomorrow, Today does not share your personal information with third parties, except Site Affiliates and as described below and otherwise specified in this Policy. Tomorrow, Today will share your personal information as follows:

• With third parties that perform functions on Tomorrow, Today’s behalf, such as maintaining and operating the Site. Tomorrow, Today does not authorize such third parties to use your information for other purposes;  
• As Tomorrow, Today believes necessary to comply with laws, statutes or regulations and/or to enforce this Policy and the Terms of Use and to protect our rights and the rights of others;  
• As necessary to process purchases and payments through the Site;  
• As required by a court or government agency or to respond to a claim by you or a third party;  
• As part of a transfer of business assets, for example in the event of a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, sale, transfer of control, joint venture or other business combination or corporate change involving Tomorrow, Today or its, parent, subsidiaries and/or affiliates; and  
• As you otherwise agree.

A court of equity, such as a bankruptcy court, may also have the authority to share your personal information or transfer it to third parties without your permission.

Subpoenas. Tomorrow, Today may respond to any subpoena received from a government agency without prior notice to you. Unless prohibited by law or by a court order, Tomorrow, Today will use reasonable efforts to notify you of any subpoena received from any other party (e.g., for civil litigation) that requires Tomorrow, Today to disclose your identity and will wait ten (10) days, or a lesser amount of time as required by the deadline in the subpoena before providing the requested information.

Except as expressly stated in this Policy, Tomorrow, Today does not share your personal information with third parties unless you “opt-in” to such disclosure. Please note that if you do “opt-in” to receive communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as Tomorrow, Today does not control third parties’ use of your information. You should always review carefully the privacy policy of any party that collects your information.

We may share aggregate information with third parties. This includes demographic information such as gender or location of Site visitors, but does not include your personal information. We use this aggregate information to improve the Site and for marketing and promotional purposes, among other purposes.

**Consent to Processing in the United States**

By providing any personal information to Tomorrow, Today, Site visitors in Canada and the European Union consent to this Policy and to the transfer of such personal information across international borders in the course of Tomorrow, Today’s standard business operations, including, without limitation, the collection, storage and processing of such personal information in the United States of America.

**Correction/Update Procedure**

If you want to view, delete or modify your personal information, you may do so:

• Through your profile privacy settings – see  
<http://www.thisis50.com/profiles/profile/privacySettings>  
• Sending an email to: info@thisisfifty.com; or  
• By mail to the following address:  
Correct/Update Personal Information  
Tomorrow, Today Entertainment, Inc.  
c/o Robins Kaplan LLP  
601 Lexington Avenue  
New York, NY 10022 USA

You may also choose to opt-out of receiving emails from the Site by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email, or by contacting us as provided above. Messages you receive through short message service (SMS), instant messaging or other than through email may not include an unsubscribe option. You can opt-out of such messages through the methods described above.

Tomorrow, Today reserves the right to verify the identity of any person making such a request or a request to delete or modify personal information; provided, however, that Tomorrow, Today will have no liability of any kind resulting from false or erroneous requests or any change or deletion made by Tomorrow, Today for any reason. Tomorrow, Today reserves the right to decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort or jeopardize the privacy of others. Personal information collected and transferred to back-up or archival storage may be retained indefinitely. Tomorrow, Today may also retain unmodified information as necessary for business purposes and as required under applicable laws, statutes and regulations.

**Links**

The Site may contain links to other websites. Tomorrow, Today has no control over, and makes no representations whatsoever regarding, such other websites or the products and services offered by or through websites accessed through links on the Site, even those with which Tomorrow, Today may have an affiliation. If you decide to access third party sites linked through the Site, you do so at your own risk. You should carefully review the privacy policy and terms of use of any such site.

**Security**

Tomorrow, Today has reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. While Tomorrow, Today strives to protect your personal information, it cannot ensure, and does not warrant, the security of any information or data. Communication via the Internet is not failsafe, and there is always a possibility that data may be lost or intercepted by unauthorized parties during transmission or after receipt. You agree that Tomorrow, Today will have no liability whatsoever in connection with any lost or intercepted data or information.

**Conditions of Use**

Your access to and use of the Site is subject to this Policy and the [Terms of Use](http://www.thisis50.com/main/authorization/termsOfService?noBack=1), including, without limitation, limitations on damages and the applicability of the law of the State of New York, USA and resolution of disputes through binding arbitration.

**Contacting Tomorrow, Today**

If you have questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices please contact us:

Tomorrow, Today Entertainment, Inc.  
c/o Robins Kaplan LLP  
601 Lexington Avenue  
New York, NY 10022 USA  
Email: info@thisisfifty.com
